var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "وَآبَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their forefathers",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "waābāahum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَبَىٰ",
        "answer": "but refuse",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fa-abā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتُونَكَ",
        "answer": "they come to you",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "yatūnaka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَوْا",
        "answer": "they have come",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "ataw",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثَامًا",
        "answer": "a penalty",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "athāman",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُجَاجٌ",
        "answer": "(and) bitter",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ujājun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٍ",
        "answer": "payment",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "ajrin",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذْ",
        "answer": "He has taken",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "yattakhidh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "Yet they have taken",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "wa-ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَّخِذَ",
        "answer": "we take",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "nattakhidha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذْتُ",
        "answer": "I had taken",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhtu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَّخِذْ",
        "answer": "I had taken",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "attakhidh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "took",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذُونَكَ",
        "answer": "they take you",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "yattakhidhūnaka",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذَ",
        "answer": "takes",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "ittakhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذَ",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "yattakhidha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرُونَ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "ākharūna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرَ",
        "answer": "another",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "ākhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَاهُ",
        "answer": "his brother",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "akhāhu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "[when]",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصِيلًا",
        "answer": "and evening",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣīlan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِفْكٌ",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "if'kun",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُ",
        "answer": "eat",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "yakulu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُ",
        "answer": "he may eat",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "yakulu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "[surely] ate",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "layakulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(is) but",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(are) except",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "Who",
        "pcklId": "848",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who ",
        "pcklId": "849",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "850",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "851",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "Who",
        "pcklId": "852",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "853",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "854",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "855",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "856",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "857",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "858",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one whom",
        "pcklId": "859",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "860",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "861",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "862",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "863",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "864",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who",
        "pcklId": "865",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "Who",
        "pcklId": "866",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "867",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) those who",
        "pcklId": "868",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "869",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "870",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "871",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "872",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "873",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "874",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "875",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "876",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "alīman",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَتِنَا",
        "answer": "our gods",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "ālihatinā",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَهُ",
        "answer": "(as) his god",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "ilāhahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهًا",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "ilāhan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "1935",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has sent",
        "pcklId": "1936",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "1937",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1938",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has forbidden",
        "pcklId": "1939",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will replace",
        "pcklId": "1940",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1941",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1942",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "442",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "443",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "444",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "445",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "[to]",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to Us",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْمُرُنَا",
        "answer": "you order us",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "tamurunā",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمَامًا",
        "answer": "a leader",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "imāman",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنَ",
        "answer": "and believes",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "tlit": "waāmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْإِنْسَانِ",
        "answer": "to the man",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "lil'insāni",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنَاسِيَّ",
        "answer": "and men",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "wa-anāsiyya",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the former people",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "of (the) Verses",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرَيْنِ",
        "answer": "the two seas",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-baḥrayni",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَدِّلُ",
        "answer": "Allah will replace",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yubaddilu",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُرُوجًا",
        "answer": "constellations",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "burūjan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَارَكَ",
        "answer": "Blessed is He",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tabāraka",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَارَكَ",
        "answer": "Blessed is He",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tabāraka",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَارَكَ",
        "answer": "Blessed is He",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tabāraka",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُشْرًا",
        "answer": "(as) glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "bush'ran",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشَرًا",
        "answer": "human being",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "basharan",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُشْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "bush'rā",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَشِّرًا",
        "answer": "(as) a bearer of glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "mubashiran",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعَثَ",
        "answer": "Allah has sent",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "baʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبَعَثْنَا",
        "answer": "surely, We (would) have raised",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "labaʿathnā",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعِيدٍ",
        "answer": "far",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "baʿīdin",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَكُمْ",
        "answer": "some of you",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "baʿḍakum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "for others",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "libaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْبَغِي",
        "answer": "it was proper",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yanbaghī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُكْرَةً",
        "answer": "morning",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "buk'ratan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلْدَةً",
        "answer": "(to) a land",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "baldatan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُورًا",
        "answer": "ruined",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "būran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبِيتُونَ",
        "answer": "spend (the) night",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yabītūna",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among them",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمَا",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "baynahumā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمَا",
        "answer": "(is) between them",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "baynahumā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَّرْنَا",
        "answer": "We destroyed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tabbarnā",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتْبِيرًا",
        "answer": "(with) destruction",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tatbīran",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "you follow",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "repents",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "repents",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتُوبُ",
        "answer": "turns",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yatūbu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَابًا",
        "answer": "(with) repentance",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "matāban",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنُثَبِّتَ",
        "answer": "that We may strengthen",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "linuthabbita",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُبُورًا",
        "answer": "(for) destruction",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "thubūran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُبُورًا",
        "answer": "(for) destruction",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "thubūran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُبُورًا",
        "answer": "(for) destructions",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "thubūran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the criminals",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "lil'muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the criminals",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجْزَوْنَ",
        "answer": "will be awarded",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yuj'zawna",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءً",
        "answer": "a reward",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "jazāan",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "(could have) made",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "and He (could) make",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "wayajʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have made",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We will make them",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "fajaʿalnāhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have made",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We appointed",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We made them",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnāhum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَجَعَلَهُ",
        "answer": "surely He (could) have made it",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "lajaʿalahu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We made",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "made",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and made",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and He has made",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلَهُ",
        "answer": "and has made (for) him",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "fajaʿalahu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "has placed",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and has placed",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "made",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاجْعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and make us",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "wa-ij'ʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُمْلَةً",
        "answer": "all at once",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "jum'latan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّةٌ",
        "answer": "a garden",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "jannatun",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "gardens ",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّةُ",
        "answer": "Garden",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "jannatu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاهِدْهُمْ",
        "answer": "and strive (against) them",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wajāhid'hum",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِهَادًا",
        "answer": "a striving",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "jihādan",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلُونَ",
        "answer": "the ignorant ones",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-jāhilūna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءُوا",
        "answer": "they (have) produced",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "jāū",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَنِي",
        "answer": "it (had) come to me",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "jāanī",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We bring you",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "ji'nāka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجْرًا",
        "answer": "A partition",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ḥij'ran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحِجْرًا",
        "answer": "and a partition",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "waḥij'ran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحْجُورًا",
        "answer": "forbidden",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "maḥjūran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحْجُورًا",
        "answer": "forbidden",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "maḥjūran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "Allah has forbidden",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْسَبُ",
        "answer": "do you think",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "taḥsabu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسُنَتْ",
        "answer": "Good",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥasunat",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "and a better",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحْسَنَ",
        "answer": "and (the) best",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥsana",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(with) good ones",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "ḥasanātin",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْشُرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "He will gather them",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yaḥshuruhum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْشَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'sharūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(will be) truly",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "by right",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَمْدِهِ",
        "answer": "with His Praise",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "biḥamdihi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينَ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ḥīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنُحْيِيَ",
        "answer": "That We may give life",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "linuḥ'yiya",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيِّ",
        "answer": "the Ever-Living",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayi",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيَاةً",
        "answer": "life",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "ḥayatan",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحِيَّةً",
        "answer": "(with) greetings",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "taḥiyyatan",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "khabīran",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "(as He is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "khabīran",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَذُولًا",
        "answer": "a deserter",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khadhūlan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخِرُّوا",
        "answer": "fall",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yakhirrū",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاطَبَهُمُ",
        "answer": "address them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khāṭabahumu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَخْلُدْ",
        "answer": "and he will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wayakhlud",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخُلْدِ",
        "answer": "(of) Eternity",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-khul'di",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "they will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "Will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلْفَةً",
        "answer": "(in) succession",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "khil'fatan",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَلَقَ",
        "answer": "and He (has) created",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "wakhalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقُونَ",
        "answer": "they create",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "yakhluqūna",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْلَقُونَ",
        "answer": "are created",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "yukh'laqūna",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "(to those) We created",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "khalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "has created",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "(as) a friend",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "khalīlan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(will be in) a better",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعَوْا",
        "answer": "they will call",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "daʿaw",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُوا",
        "answer": "call",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "tadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادْعُوا",
        "answer": "but call",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "wa-id'ʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "invoke",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "yadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُعَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your prayer (is to Him)",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "duʿāukum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "an indication",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "dalīlan",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَدَمَّرْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "Then We destroyed them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fadammarnāhum",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْمِيرًا",
        "answer": "(with) destruction",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tadmīran",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِكَ",
        "answer": "besides You",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "dūnika",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذُرِّيَّاتِنَا",
        "answer": "and our offspring",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wadhurriyyātinā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِّرُوا",
        "answer": "they are reminded",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "dhukkirū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَذَّكَّرُوا",
        "answer": "that they may remember",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "liyadhakkarū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذَّكَّرَ",
        "answer": "remember",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "yadhakkara",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّكْرَ",
        "answer": "the Message",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "l-dhik'ra",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّكْرِ",
        "answer": "the Reminder",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "l-dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذُنُوبِ",
        "answer": "regarding the sins",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "bidhunūbi",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "اذْهَبَا",
        "answer": "Go both of you",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "idh'habā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُذِقْهُ",
        "answer": "We will make him taste",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "nudhiq'hu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "it sees them",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "ra-athum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "we see",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "narā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْنَ",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "yarawna",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْنَهَا",
        "answer": "see it",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "yarawnahā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَوْكَ",
        "answer": "they see you",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "ra-awka",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْنَ",
        "answer": "they will see",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "yarawna",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتَ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "ara-ayta",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَ",
        "answer": "see",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "tara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "551",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "552",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "553",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا رَبِّ",
        "answer": "O my Lord",
        "pcklId": "554",
        "tlit": "yārabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "555",
        "tlit": "birabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "556",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "557",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "558",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "559",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "before their Lord",
        "pcklId": "560",
        "tlit": "lirabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "561",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "562",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "563",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "564",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَتَّلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We have recited it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "warattalnāhu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْتِيلًا",
        "answer": "(with distinct) recitation",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tartīlan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلًا",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "rajulan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجُونَ",
        "answer": "expect",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yarjūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجُونَ",
        "answer": "expecting",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yarjūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "for the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "lilrraḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "to the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "lilrraḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "raḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمًا",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "raḥīman",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمًا",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "raḥīman",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسِّ",
        "answer": "(of) Ar-rass",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-rasi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلَ",
        "answer": "sends",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "arsala",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We sent you",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "arsalnāka",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "Messenger",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولِ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "l-rasūli",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّسُلَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "l-rusula",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "(as) a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّيَاحَ",
        "answer": "the winds",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-riyāḥa",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "desires",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "desires",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَفِيرًا",
        "answer": "and roaring",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wazafīran",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزْنُونَ",
        "answer": "commit unlawful sexual intercourse",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaznūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجِنَا",
        "answer": "our spouses",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "azwājinā",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزُورًا",
        "answer": "and a lie",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wazūran",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزُّورَ",
        "answer": "(to) the falsehood",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-zūra",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَادَهُمْ",
        "answer": "And it increases them",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wazādahum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْأَلُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I ask (of) you",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "asalukum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْأَلْ",
        "answer": "so ask",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "fasal",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْئُولًا",
        "answer": "requested",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "masūlan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبَاتًا",
        "answer": "a rest",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "subātan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَبِّحْ",
        "answer": "and glorify",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wasabbiḥ",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَكَ",
        "answer": "Glory be to You",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānaka",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "a way",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلَ",
        "answer": "(from) the way",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "l-sabīla",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "a way",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(from the) way",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(from the) way",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(from the) way",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "a way",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِتَّةِ",
        "answer": "six",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "sittati",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْجُدُوا",
        "answer": "Prostrate",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "us'judū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنَسْجُدُ",
        "answer": "Should we prostrate",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "anasjudu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُجَّدًا",
        "answer": "prostrating",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "sujjadan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْحُورًا",
        "answer": "bewitched",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "masḥūran",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِرَاجًا",
        "answer": "a lamp",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sirājan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّرَّ",
        "answer": "the secret",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-sira",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْرِفُوا",
        "answer": "(are) not extravagant",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yus'rifū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسَاطِيرُ",
        "answer": "Tales",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "asāṭīru",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعِيرًا",
        "answer": "a Blazing Fire",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "saʿīran",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُسْقِيَهُ",
        "answer": "and We give drink",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wanus'qiyahu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاكِنًا",
        "answer": "stationary",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "sākinan",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامًا",
        "answer": "Peace",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "salāman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَلَامًا",
        "answer": "and peace",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "wasalāman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعُوا",
        "answer": "they will hear",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "samiʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "hear",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "l-samāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the skies",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاءَتْ",
        "answer": "(is) an evil",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "sāat",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّوْءِ",
        "answer": "(of) evil",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-sawi",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their evil deeds",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "sayyiātihim",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسَّاعَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "bil-sāʿati",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسَّاعَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "bil-sāʿati",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْوَاقِ",
        "answer": "the markets",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-aswāqi",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْوَاقِ",
        "answer": "the markets",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-aswāqi",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "He established Himself",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "is'tawā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرٌّ",
        "answer": "(are the) worst",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "sharrun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرِيكٌ",
        "answer": "a partner",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "sharīkun",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشَقَّقُ",
        "answer": "will split open",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tashaqqaqu",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُكُورًا",
        "answer": "to be thankful",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "shukūran",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسَ",
        "answer": "the sun",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-shamsa",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْهَدُونَ",
        "answer": "bear witness",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yashhadūna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "He willed",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُونَ",
        "answer": "they wish",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "yashāūna",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "He willed",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْنَا",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "shi'nā",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "(that) whoever wills",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَصْبِرُونَ",
        "answer": "will you have patience",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ataṣbirūna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَرْنَا",
        "answer": "we had been steadfast",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ṣabarnā",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَرُوا",
        "answer": "they were patient",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ṣabarū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(The) companions",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْحَابَ",
        "answer": "and (the) dwellers",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣḥāba",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "اصْرِفْ",
        "answer": "Avert",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "iṣ'rif",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرَّفْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have distributed it",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ṣarrafnāhu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرْفًا",
        "answer": "(to) avert",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ṣarfan",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteous (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُمًّا",
        "answer": "deaf",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ṣumman",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصِهْرًا",
        "answer": "and marriage relationship",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waṣih'ran",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "and destination",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wamaṣīran",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرَبُوا",
        "answer": "they set forth",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ḍarabū",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرَبْنَا",
        "answer": "We have set forth",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ḍarabnā",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضُرُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "harms them",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yaḍurruhum",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرًّا",
        "answer": "any harm",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "ḍarran",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضَاعَفْ",
        "answer": "Will be doubled",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yuḍāʿaf",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "but they have gone astray",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "faḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "went astray",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضْلَلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "[you] mislead",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "aḍlaltum",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلَّنِي",
        "answer": "he led me astray",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "aḍallanī",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيُضِلُّنَا",
        "answer": "[surely] misled us",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "layuḍillunā",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَضَلُّ",
        "answer": "and most astray",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "wa-aḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلُّ",
        "answer": "(is) more astray",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "aḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلُّ",
        "answer": "(are) more astray",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "aḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَيِّقًا",
        "answer": "narrow",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ḍayyiqan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّعَامَ",
        "answer": "[the] food",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-ṭaʿāma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّعَامَ",
        "answer": "food",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-ṭaʿāma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَهُورًا",
        "answer": "pure",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ṭahūran",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُطِعِ",
        "answer": "obey",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "tuṭiʿi",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they are able (to find)",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "you are able",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "tastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظِّلَّ",
        "answer": "the shadow",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-ẓila",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمْ",
        "answer": "does wrong",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "yaẓlim",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلْمًا",
        "answer": "an injustice",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "ẓul'man",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoer",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "lilẓẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهِيرًا",
        "answer": "a helper",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ẓahīran",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْبَأُ",
        "answer": "will care",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿba-u",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "they worship",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "yaʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "But they worship",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "wayaʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَبْدِهِ",
        "answer": "His slave",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "ʿabdihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِي",
        "answer": "My slaves",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "ʿibādī",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) His slaves",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِبَادُ",
        "answer": "And (the) slaves",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "waʿibādu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْتَدْنَا",
        "answer": "and We have prepared",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿtadnā",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْتَدْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have prepared",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿtadnā",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَتَوْا",
        "answer": "and (become) insolent",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waʿataw",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُتُوًّا",
        "answer": "(with) insolence",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ʿutuwwan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوًّا",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَهَا",
        "answer": "its punishment",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābahā",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذْبٌ",
        "answer": "palatable",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "ʿadhbun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "the Throne ",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسِيرًا",
        "answer": "difficult",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿasīran",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعَضُّ",
        "answer": "will bite",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaʿaḍḍu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "will know",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "to the worlds",
        "pcklId": "508",
        "tlit": "lil'ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "they did",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "ʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلَ",
        "answer": "and does",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "waʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلَ",
        "answer": "and does",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "waʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلٍ",
        "answer": "(the) deed(s)",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "ʿamalin",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلًا",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "ʿamalan",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعُمْيَانًا",
        "answer": "and blind",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "waʿum'yānan",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَادًا",
        "answer": "And Ad",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "waʿādan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعَانَهُ",
        "answer": "and helped him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿānahu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْيُنٍ",
        "answer": "(to) our eyes",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "aʿyunin",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغُرْفَةَ",
        "answer": "the Chamber",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ghur'fata",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْرَقْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We drowned them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "aghraqnāhum",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَرَامًا",
        "answer": "inseparable",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "gharāman",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورًا",
        "answer": "Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "ghafūran",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورًا",
        "answer": "Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "ghafūran",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغَمَامِ",
        "answer": "with the clouds",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "bil-ghamāmi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَغَيُّظًا",
        "answer": "raging",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taghayyuẓan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُؤَادَكَ",
        "answer": "your heart",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fuādaka",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةً",
        "answer": "a trial",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "fit'natan",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُرَاتٌ",
        "answer": "and sweet",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "furātun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُرْقَانَ",
        "answer": "the Criterion",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-fur'qāna",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَاهُ",
        "answer": "he invented it",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "if'tarāhu",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْسِيرًا",
        "answer": "explanation",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tafsīran",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلْ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "yafʿal",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُلَانًا",
        "answer": "that one",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fulānan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبَضْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We withdraw it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "qabaḍnāhu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْضًا",
        "answer": "a withdrawal",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "qabḍan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "qablaka",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْتُرُوا",
        "answer": "and are not stingy",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaqturū",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْتُلُونَ",
        "answer": "[they] kill",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "yaqtulūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَدَّرَهُ",
        "answer": "and determined it",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "faqaddarahu",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "qadīran",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْدِيرًا",
        "answer": "(with) determination",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "taqdīran",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَدِمْنَا",
        "answer": "And We will proceed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waqadim'nā",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنُ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-qur'ānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرَّةَ",
        "answer": "comfort",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "qurrata",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقَرًّا",
        "answer": "abode",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "mus'taqarran",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقَرًّا",
        "answer": "abode",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "mus'taqarran",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقَرًّا",
        "answer": "(is) the settlement",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "mus'taqarran",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُرُونًا",
        "answer": "and generations",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "waqurūnan",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقَرَّنِينَ",
        "answer": "bound in chains",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "muqarranīna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَرْيَةِ",
        "answer": "the town",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-qaryati",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "town",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُصُورًا",
        "answer": "palaces",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "quṣūran",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَمَرًا",
        "answer": "and a moon",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waqamaran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "1029",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1030",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1031",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1032",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And say",
        "pcklId": "1033",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1034",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "and He will say",
        "pcklId": "1035",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They say",
        "pcklId": "1036",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "1037",
        "tlit": "taqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "1038",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "and they will say",
        "pcklId": "1039",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "he will say",
        "pcklId": "1040",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "1041",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "1042",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "Then We said",
        "pcklId": "1043",
        "tlit": "faqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1044",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "1045",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They say",
        "pcklId": "1046",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "1047",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "1048",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "1049",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1050",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوَامًا",
        "answer": "moderate",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "qawāman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "people",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِي",
        "answer": "my people",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "qawmī",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) people",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "waqawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "532",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِيَامًا",
        "answer": "and standing",
        "pcklId": "594",
        "tlit": "waqiyāman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُقَامًا",
        "answer": "and resting place",
        "pcklId": "619",
        "tlit": "wamuqāman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُقَامًا",
        "answer": "and a resting place",
        "pcklId": "620",
        "tlit": "wamuqāman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقِيلًا",
        "answer": "resting-place",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "maqīlan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "they have become arrogant",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكْتَتَبَهَا",
        "answer": "which he has had written",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ik'tatabahā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرُ",
        "answer": "most",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "aktharu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "they deny",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "they deny you",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "kadhabūkum",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "have denied",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "they denied",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have denied",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "kadhabtum",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِرَامًا",
        "answer": "(as) dignified ones",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "kirāman",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرُ",
        "answer": "the disbeliever",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "l-kāfiru",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُفُورًا",
        "answer": "disbelief",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "kufūran",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "459",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "460",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "But sufficient is",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wakafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "And sufficient is",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wakafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "for every",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلًّا",
        "answer": "And each",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "wakullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلًّا",
        "answer": "and each",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "wakullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَنْزٌ",
        "answer": "a treasure",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "kanzun",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادَ",
        "answer": "He would have almost",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "kāda",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَكُونَ",
        "answer": "that he may be",
        "pcklId": "815",
        "tlit": "liyakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "He has",
        "pcklId": "816",
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "817",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَكُونَ",
        "answer": "then he be",
        "pcklId": "818",
        "tlit": "fayakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "819",
        "tlit": "takūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "It will be",
        "pcklId": "820",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "It is",
        "pcklId": "821",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "it was proper",
        "pcklId": "822",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and became",
        "pcklId": "823",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "824",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And (it will) be",
        "pcklId": "825",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "826",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "they [were]",
        "pcklId": "827",
        "tlit": "yakūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they are",
        "pcklId": "828",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "829",
        "tlit": "takūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "830",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and is",
        "pcklId": "831",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "832",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "but are",
        "pcklId": "833",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "834",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُ",
        "answer": "will be",
        "pcklId": "835",
        "tlit": "yakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانٍ",
        "answer": "a place",
        "pcklId": "1374",
        "tlit": "makānin",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) a place",
        "pcklId": "1375",
        "tlit": "makānan",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) position",
        "pcklId": "1376",
        "tlit": "makānan",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَاسًا",
        "answer": "(as) a covering",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "libāsan",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِزَامًا",
        "answer": "the inevitable (punishment)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "lizāman",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّغْوِ",
        "answer": "by futility",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bil-laghwi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْقَ",
        "answer": "will meet",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yalqa",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُلَقَّوْنَ",
        "answer": "and they will be met",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wayulaqqawna",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُلْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "is delivered",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "yul'qā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُلْقُوا",
        "answer": "they are thrown",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "ul'qū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "(the) meeting with Us",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "liqāanā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَّعْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "You gave them comforts",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "mattaʿtahum",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْثَالَ",
        "answer": "the similitudes",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "l-amthāla",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَثَلٍ",
        "answer": "with an example",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "bimathalin",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْثَالَ",
        "answer": "the examples",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "l-amthāla",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَدَّ",
        "answer": "He extends",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "madda",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَجَ",
        "answer": "(has) released",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "maraja",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرُّوا",
        "answer": "they pass",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "marrū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرُّوا",
        "answer": "they pass",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "marrū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَمْشِي",
        "answer": "and walk",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wayamshī",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَمْشُونَ",
        "answer": "and walked",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wayamshūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْشُونَ",
        "answer": "walk",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yamshūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمْطِرَتْ",
        "answer": "was showered",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "um'ṭirat",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَطَرَ",
        "answer": "(with) a rain",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "maṭara",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِلْحٌ",
        "answer": "salty",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mil'ḥun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they possess",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yamlikūna",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they control",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yamlikūna",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكِ",
        "answer": "the dominion",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-mul'ki",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكُ",
        "answer": "The Sovereignty",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "al-mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكٌ",
        "answer": "an Angel",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "malakun",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةَ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "l-malāikata",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "l-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُمْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "are dictated",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tum'lā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمُوتُ",
        "answer": "does not die",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yamūtu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْتًا",
        "answer": "death",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "mawtan",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيْتًا",
        "answer": "dead",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "maytan",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءً",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "māan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the water",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-māi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبِيٍّ",
        "answer": "Prophet",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "nabiyyin",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنْثُورًا",
        "answer": "dispersed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "manthūran",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرًا",
        "answer": "a warner ",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "nadhīran",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرًا",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "nadhīran",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرًا",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "nadhīran",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذِيرًا",
        "answer": "and a warner",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "wanadhīran",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "sent down",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "nazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُزِّلَ",
        "answer": "and (will be) sent down",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wanuzzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُزِّلَ",
        "answer": "was revealed",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "nuzzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَهُ",
        "answer": "Has sent it down",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "anzalahu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "is sent down",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "are sent down",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We send down",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "wa-anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلًا",
        "answer": "descending",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "tanzīlan",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسَبًا",
        "answer": "blood relationship",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "nasaban",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسُوا",
        "answer": "they forgot",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "nasū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُشُورًا",
        "answer": "resurrection",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nushūran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُشُورًا",
        "answer": "Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "nushūran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُشُورًا",
        "answer": "a resurrection",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "nushūran",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرًا",
        "answer": "(to) help",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "naṣran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "and a Helper",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "wanaṣīran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "See",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالْأَنْعَامِ",
        "answer": "like cattle",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "kal-anʿāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَامًا",
        "answer": "cattle",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "anʿāman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفُورًا",
        "answer": "(in) aversion",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "nufūran",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for themselves",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "li-anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّفْسَ",
        "answer": "the soul",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "l-nafsa",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْفَعُهُمْ",
        "answer": "not profits them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yanfaʿuhum",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْعًا",
        "answer": "any benefit",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "nafʿan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفَقُوا",
        "answer": "they spend",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "anfaqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنِيرًا",
        "answer": "shining",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "munīran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for mankind",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّوْمَ",
        "answer": "and the sleep",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wal-nawma",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَبَاءً",
        "answer": "(as) dust",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "habāan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَهْجُورًا",
        "answer": "(as) a forsaken thing",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "mahjūran",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادِيًا",
        "answer": "(as) a Guide",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "hādiyan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُزُوًا",
        "answer": "(in) mockery",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "huzuwan",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَوْنًا",
        "answer": "(in) humbleness",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "hawnan",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهَانًا",
        "answer": "humiliated",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "muhānan",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَوَاهُ",
        "answer": "his own desire",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "hawāhu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their faces",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "wujūhihim",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدًا",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wāḥidan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "all at once",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزِيرًا",
        "answer": "(as) an assistant",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wazīran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُعِدَ",
        "answer": "is promised",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wuʿida",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدًا",
        "answer": "a promise",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "waʿdan",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) the righteous",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "for the righteous",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَكَّلْ",
        "answer": "And put your trust",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "watawakkal",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلًا",
        "answer": "a guardian",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wakīlan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدًا",
        "answer": "a son",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "waladan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "protectors",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَبْ",
        "answer": "Grant",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "hab",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "his hands",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "yadayhi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "yaday",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسِيرًا",
        "answer": "gradual",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yasīran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "this day",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a Day",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "yawman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "periods",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "25",
        "ayah": "69"
    }
]; 
export default words;